(Sheldon:)I suggest you look
for long-lost relatives
(Sheldon:)either in Armenia or Lebanon.
(Leonard:)Listen to me, Sheldon.
(Leonard:)I am not going to Lebanon
(Leonard:)to return
Super Mario Bros. the movie!
Anyway, it might be fun.
You love hummus.
(Leonard:)Why isn't this bothering you?
(Leonard:)Isn't your brain getting itchy?
(Leonard:)This is on your card.
(Leonard:)This could be ruining
your credit score!
(Leonard:)Why isn't this making you crazy?
(Sheldon:)Leonard...
(Sheldon:)I have something to tell you,
(Sheldon:)but I want you to promise
not to flip out.
(Leonard:)What?
(Sheldon:)Seven years ago,
(Sheldon:)I found out the DVD was late
and I paid for it.